[MUSIC]
(muffled speaking)
(clicking)
(click)
[ Pause ]
(silence)
(clicking)
(click)
[ Pause ]
(silence)
(clicking)
[ Pause ]
(clapping)
(laughs)
(clicking)
(mouse clicking)
(click)
(clicking)
(silence)
(click)
(clicking)
(laughs)
(clapping)
(clicking)
(silence)
(chuckling)
(clicking)
(clapping)
(crying)
(laughing)
(clapping)
(laughter)
(coughing)
(clapping)
(laughing)
(audience laughing)
(clapping)
(clicking)
(audience laughing)
(coughing)
(laughter)
(audience laughing)
(clapping)
[ Pause ]
(laughter)
(crying)
(audience laughing)
[laughter]
(clapping)
(crying)
(clicking)
[ Laughter ]
[laughter]
(crying)
(laughing)
(audience laughing)
(clapping)
(clicking)
(crying)
(laughing)
(clicking)
(crying)
(clapping)
(chuckling)
(crying)
[laughter]
(coughing)
(crying)
(clicking)
[ Pause ]
(crying)
(coughing)
(laughing)
(crying)
(clicking)
(laughing)
(crying)
(clapping)
(laughing)
(crying)
[coughing]
(coughing)
(clicking)
(chattering)
(coughing)
(clicking)
(crying)
(coughing)
(panting)
(crying)
(coughing)
(clicking)
(crying)
(coughing)
[laughter]
(audience laughing)
(crying)
(coughing)
(clicking)
(crying)
(laughing)
(clicking)
(coughing)
(crying)
(clicking)
(coughing)
(clapping)
(crying)
(clicking)
(coughing)
(clapping)
(clicking)
(crying)
(coughing)
(clicking)
(clapping)
(coughing)
(clicking)
(clapping)
(laughing)
(clicking)
(clapping)
(crying)
(laughing)
(clapping)
(clicking)
(crying)
(laughing)
(chattering)
(crying)
(laughing)
(clapping)
(muffled speaking)
(laughing)
(crying)
(clapping)
(laughing)
(crying)
(clicking)
(clapping)
(muffled speaking)
(clicking)
[clicking]
(clapping)
(muffled speaking)
Okay.
(clicking)
(laughing)
(crying)
[ Laughter ]
(clapping)
(muffled speaking)
[ Laughter ]
(clapping)
(muffled speaking)
[inaudible]
(chatter)
(muffled speaking)
[inaudible]
(speaking in foreign language)
(clapping)
(chattering)
[inaudible]
(speaking in foreign language)
(muffled speaking)
(indistinct)
[inaudible]
(muffled speaking)
[ Inaudible ]
(crowd murmuring)
(clapping)
(crying)
(muffled speaking)
(clicking)
(laughs)
(clapping)
[inaudible]
[clapping]
(clapping)
(mumbling)
[inaudible]
I want you to be there when you're in a peace world.
You're going to be there with us.
You're going to die when you're in a fight,
and you're going to die when you're in a peace world.
You're going to die when you're in a peace world.
I want you to be there when you're in a peace world.
You're going to be there when you're in a peace world.
(muffled speaking)
[inaudible]
(clapping)
(muffled speaking)
(chattering)
[inaudible]
(clapping)
(crying)
(clicking)
[inaudible]
(clapping)
(muffled speaking)
[inaudible]
(crowd murmuring)
(muffled speaking)
[inaudible]
[ Pause ]
[ Inaudible ]
I think you realize that after you have started,
I think you have to be there one week to take care of your kids,
and you are fine.
Why are you tired of the very fine times?
You have to be able to be tired, I think you have to be there
and you have to be able to come out.
You have to be tired of the same things.
But shall it be just a day of peace, what you have to follow.
You can take a day of peace, take a day of peace.
So why you take a day of peace, take a day of peace.
What you have to tell is, what you have to follow.
You have to follow. You have to live.
It is like living in a city that you want.
You have to live in a city that you have to follow.
(speaking in foreign language)
[inaudible]
I like this.
We made it to the bottom of the table.
(speaking in foreign language)
(inaudible)
I'm going to say, "One side, very few, four days."
So, I'm going to say, "One side, very few, four days."
So, I'm going to say, "One side, five, five, very few days, four days, four days, four days."
So, I'm going to say, "One side, very few days."
So, we're going to feel a certain feeling.
That's very good for you.
Because we can focus on what I believe in,
in your presence,
when I'm feeling a certain feeling.
We can focus on what I believe in,
in the right place to be,
in the right place to be, in the right place.
And I like you, yes?
And we say, yes, we can focus on.
And I say, that's very good.
And later, I just know, really not to say, oh, please, please,
not know.
Please, please, Mr. Brown, please, please.
Please, please, please.
The government is not going to do it.
The climate is not going to do it.
The government is going to do it a lot.
A lot.
And then, you are going to do it.
And then, you are going to do it a lot.
I'm going to get a piece of this.
Believe it, let's be like this.
So that's the baby piece.
What is like like a million years ago for this?
Oh, let's be like this.
What's the baby piece for this?
I'm going to get a piece.
And I'm going to get a piece.
Let's go to the line.
And I say, "Hey, I'm fine."
So I'm going down for a minute.
I need to do it for a minute.
Just like that.
You can ask me, "How do you feel about this?"
Or, "How do you feel about this?"
I need to do it for a minute.
[inaudible]
No, let's go back to you.
You can do it, Father.
You know you have to do it.
You fall asleep to me,
and you don't eat the munchies and lads, all the lads,
and you go and have a human sleep.
And you don't have to do it.
You don't have to do it, Father.
But all you need, Father, is God's duty, Father.
We need to be blessed with His Father, Father.
All right.
You need to be blessed with His Father.
You need to be able to have Your love.
You need to be able to keep your love.
You need to find us what they're doing.
They need to find us what they're doing.
Brother, brother, brother, brother.
Brother, brother.
[ Inaudible ]
[inaudible]
(inaudible)
I don't know if you're going to get it.
I want you to go through the...
I mean, you're going to be a little bit younger,
you're going to be a little bit older,
you're going to be a little bit older.
You're going to be a little bit older.
I want you to go through the...
>> [INAUDIBLE]
And I will be able to address the question of the situation. And if we are going to be
Anthony,
[ Pause ]
(clicking)
(Applause)
I am talking, that you are in the United States, by and by and by and by and by and by and by.
the country, the country, the Italian support. So we have asked, now, the United States, because every United States, all the reasons to be, are taught. That, you know, the United States, by and by and by and by and by.
The good things of the days of all the things, all the days of all the things.
Start it, my will.
There's not things about pouring all the things. Give a little go.
No wonder, very mostly, no further, very concerned.
I think it's very well, but I'll not go and end up over again.
To me, we are giving things to our knowledge.
Not always, always, but, after all, what, when I was born.
You see, he consumptionally again.
You, sir, have come, you thought, or he died for this animal.
You can't move, he'll get out of the house. No, this morning's up.
There's been ten hours, he'll suppose, he'll be, probably, all together.
And I thought, I thought, he'd be, you know,
that this part of the mange of the Lord himself.
Now, my Lord, both men, are His legs.
Then what are the names of Allah?
They're all born.
That is the false goal. That is the way that you get married to all.
That is where, that is the partner, that is the man, the people, the man, the people.
The sallam, the people, the family, the people.
These are the men of Allah.
They do have a creation of His legs, and He will be brought to Allah.
One of these men, for God's legs, which are the men,]
live to God.
In other words, Allah will dance, downfall.
Most everything comes fast asleep.
The men are always there.
In 28 hours, in three picture, 100 in four Gallops,
there was collapse happening in the inferno.
He has given a dance in a part of it, for a moment.
In a time, I was in England for that he had power.
He was for that, that's for that he was in the king, that's for all of us.
He was the last, the order of God's power.
He was the last, the option of the king of king, then he was also for all power,
In most times, in other words,
can you hold your eyes?
That's how your eyes are.
This is so, so everything.
And this is what, that is done.
Very, very, very, very.
It's not a follower.
Who's looking at something, who's looking at this place?
Those very, very, very dialogue to him.
In the form.
So we are forward.
Can you hold it?
Let's follow.
Look, let's try this forward.
Start, try, try.
Make him for character.
That is also to follow this Allah, in that word what shall it sound like?
What to do with it?
It is not what God has, what a Lord thought is, is art in it, what a life.
In that word, that what the hell of a divine is, feels, he has, was to be heard in thought.
Then it's certain for yourself that's also of a very spiritual, spiritual, spiritual,
And to all who it remembers is, was Allah, who is wrong,
people are right, or either, people are right.
That is, he's got intellectual, sexual power,
the spiritual, sexual, all these positions,
all who he is searching the public force.
And as you go on, he says, all the days, all just men,
even our body parts, our hands, our hands, and you explain it.
The Lord is with us against us. He is with us against us.
All for a hymn to us. Two or three or four, perhaps three or four.
For two weeks, karantan te el kamforgare.
Enelings thought is number one, the meaning of the kingdom is done in a large door in relative.
That is power, a lot of power is monitored into every event, in dire and in nature.
When there is lightning, that is a manifestation of the last thing, of the sky, it is in my
sound.
When there is something else for it, when you put it freely, and it is still a very simple
way.
When it is warm, when rain comes, of time it comes, all of this, all of this, all of this
And so, because man is a man, being his head,
water, he has to come out, he also holds for a very cool man.
And meeting his nature was actualized.
Now what do you mean by actualized?
You know the piece of arrow, but this room's reparition.
It can be very hard or very cold.
But it is what we call 'fault-fault-fault', there is nothing else.
How do you make it out?
You put your fire, there is nothing else, after the house.
So, man has this thought and shall it be.
He has this dimension.
Errant, there is a lot, there is no one.
You thought there is full name.
Art is ancient.
You may have this information, you may have thought.
Which means, not just thought, there is,
there is this person thought there is full name.
For this.
When I was in the master's, I was a mountain boy.
I was born.
And when we arrived, we became a position,
all the spiritual ones.
These were churches.
We turned to our last door, master, in freedom.
Our door, in freedom.
He is without the power.
And our love, the relationship towards him.
And for me, mankind, the revelation.
Why?
You talk with the leadership of the Divine Mary.
The leaderships are so close, they forgetful men.
The leaderships are poised against the rich,
with this wild and deep, just as they do.
And although of the love, if you remind them,
you remember, Father, it's love.
Then it's all what is standing on.
You remember Allah.
All is getting asked to tell the Lord, remember the reason for the reason.
Everything comes to the inside, there is a challenge.
For the Spirit, the Spirit forget the Lord, the Spirit forget the Lord, the Spirit forget the Lord, the Spirit forget the Lord, the Spirit forget the Lord, the Spirit forget the Lord, the Spirit forget the Lord.
Now you may be glad to say, "See, if the Spirit forget the Lord, the Spirit forget the Lord."
He goes that far, part of our soul, is His limit.
That is the same as our breath, okay?
It is the same as our breath.
Same thing as we should call.
He sees that there is a very same error,
because He sees that there is a very same error,
which is only for us.
He will forget our love, our care, his soul.
We call it his heart, what he saw,
that's the number of other.
But we should say, "This is the same thing for us."
But what?
So it is all what he called, "proposgis."
He knows it.
He takes A into A, for one, that one.
You too.
You get to visit all the different things.
You're in, where you're going, where you're going.
You're not talking to yourself, you're going to follow.
You're going to visit the American experience and so on.
Now you can sit down in your prayer.
You're going to visit me.
You're going to be not talking to me.
I love you.
Now, to God ourselves, at least, there is no output, there is no tolerance of a doctrine.
There is no tolerance.
We must always be done to the ground.
Then there is quality.
Or the grains of morality are found in the ground.
These are the things which will tell us how to make our child to the title and responsible
man.
responsible manner.
The overall time is beautiful, it's a largely close to false power,
and it gives us a false power, and it's not what.
Me, sir, or how much we have of healing,
but we are comfortable to heal, or heal, or doubt,
in other words, if you are more than hungry,
you must be pleased that power is never unenacted from its soul.
And we are not always, always, so sought to. We are not going to be in. We are not going to be in the world. We are going to be in the world there. And not we cannot be here. But now, in the world, in the dark world, of through the snow.
I got pictures of how to pray.
I was supposed to say, "Laugh to the Lord, to walk this door clean."
Just sitting on our side, on the door.
Do not find it, do not forget.
If we forget, give more people what it is.
I don't care, sir.
Do not forget.
Pray to be the children of God.
But only with regularness.
And you just want to have to go up to the level of religion.
Or to be dying in the same time as you are up to the island.
And then over, you can see the middle of the night,
and after the evening, you can see the middle of the night.
Up and out, up and up.
[ Inaudible ]
What is this?
I wonder if...
If Nathan makes me into jail,
if Nathan could get his power,
or if Nathan...
or if so...
If Nathan...
or what's wrong...
if he's wrong...
to a blind party. We started really well. Because many can't die. We need to get this fight into a situation. I don't exactly know that. We can't die. And that's our total number. We can't go down to the death. Let me say, come to life. Don't get off of these. You know, we're in the middle of the middle. You need to get to the right. But it's the first time I went to a room. I wouldn't be free to meet with a doctor. I hope we can go to the middle of the room.
But I'm thinking, we still have access to the power,
even though we forget it so much.
I did, yes. But when it gets built, we'll forget it.
Yes, yes, yes.
We don't have any more words, no.
Power is more than necessary.
We don't have any power.
We don't have power all the time.
We need power to do what was before.
(laughter)
(whistling)
(muffled speaking)
I am going to take the aid from myself now.
Now, I will never get away from you.
I am not afraid of you, sir.
I am going to take the aid from myself.
I don't want to give it, you know, when I read that I went with it because my son had a good friend and he tried to lose my son.
Because you were, I really didn't make any comments.
Anita, Anita, Anita, Anita!
You're a bum fool, you're a fool, you're a coward.
I love the Africa.
No, I love the Africa.
The book is, the fact, what you understand.
You know what you are.
And so it's necessary, if all is involved in my children,
in the cause of the military knowledge,
I'll give them a pay delivery.
But you know, I'm worried about country, right?
It's worried me about the country.
You want to go for it?
Because it's very much material.
And the child is mainly not material, you have to think that way.
It shows that the military is in the country.
[inaudible]
That's all right.
(indistinct chatter)
[ Inaudible ]
[inaudible]
The truth has been of the rule of the class, the power. It's let from power. So, this is life. We will do that. It's just not no failure.
Let's see if we can read it.
(speaking in foreign language)
- You know the enemy was sent to the ground.
- But in this itself, you must rule.
They need to get the doctor down.
No, it's clear, it's clear, it's clear, it's clear.
Why, what the...
What's wrong with you, Mr. Kidzilani?
Mr. Kidzilani, what's wrong with you, Mr. Kidzilani?
Yeah, I read it on the phone.
I read it on the phone.
I'm a business leader, to me, so fantastic.
We are studying business, but not a financial investment.
Anybody can make up on a financial investment.
Send them.
And some of the companies have to be a financial investment.
They don't have to pay the money.
(speaking in foreign language)
Maybe it was time to insult me.
- Okay, great job.
Remember that sounds like you.
[buzzing]